{"data":[{"question":"If they had followed my plan, they could have done the job better with _________people and ___ money.","a":"fewer, fewer","b":"less, less","c":"less, fewer","d":"less, fewer","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Few &amp; Fewer are used with countable nouns \n- Less &amp; Little are used with non-countable nouns ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"___ terrible situation we've been having this week!","a":"What a","b":"How a","c":"What","d":"How","answer":"1","explain":"\n- What + noun phrase ( adj + noun): exclamative sentence ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"I'd like _________ information about your company, please. \"Well, you could have ___ word with the manager. That might be helpful.\"","a":"an, some","b":"some, a","c":"an, a","d":"some, some","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Information: uncountable noun- not use \"an\/a\" \n- Word: countable noun, singular- not use \"some\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"He gained his ___by selling ___ of famous authors.","a":"wealths, works","b":"wealth, work","c":"wealth, works","d":"wealths, work","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Wealth: uncountable noun, no \"s\" in plural\n\n- Works: things created by famous authors: novel of writer, painting of paiter","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Chairs are made of ___.","a":"wooden","b":"wood","c":"woods","d":"some woods","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Made of + Noun (singular)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"___ we have today!","a":"What a bad weather","b":"A bad weather","c":"What bad weather","d":"How a bad weather","answer":"3","explain":"\n- What + noun phrase ( adj + noun): exclaimative sentence \n- A: use with thing that is not specific. This case \"terrible sistuation\" is defined by \" we have\"- not use \"a\" ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"___ work has been done to improve our life.","a":"A great many","b":"Many","c":"A great deal of","d":"A large number of","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- A great deal of: a large quantity of something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"The farmer has raised ___ of _________of ___ on her farm.","a":"hundreds, head, cattle","b":"hundred, head, cattle","c":"hundreds, heads, catties","d":"hundred, heads, cattle","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Hundreds of something: a very large number of things or people\n\n- Head of cattle: number of cattle","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"___ turn yellow in fall.","a":"Leafs","b":"Leaf","c":"Leaves","d":"Leave","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Verb \"turn\" - subject is plural \n- Leaf - (plural): leaves","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"If these pants are too small, buy a bigger ___.","a":"one","b":"set","c":"pair","d":"copy","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We said \" pair of pants\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"}]}